Coco YU

Full Stack Developer - Toronto, ON

SUMMARY

I am seeking a position in full-stack development. I have been working as a software developer 5 years, I've built a strong skill set. I excel in problem-solving, adapt easily, pay great attention to detail, and have strong interpersonal skills. These abilities have played a crucial role in my collaborations with customers and cross-functional teams to set requirements, create solutions, integrate components, and implement new features successfully.

SKILLS

Languages: C#, JavaScript, PHP, HTML/CSS, Visual C#, Java, Net, jQuery, Bootstrap, JSON, XML

Back-end Languages: MySQL, MSSQL

Tools: Apache, Workbench, Window Server 2016 and 2019, integrating 3rd party solutions(API), React, Google analytics, Android studio, Xcode, Unity3D, DoTween, 3ds max, AWS, Git/GitHub, SourceTree and Wix

Familiar Knowledge: Agile Scrum methodology, MVC, UML, flow chart, Entity-Relationship Diagram (ERD), RDBS, object-oriented programming concepts, unit/integration testing, composing user manuals, and addressing software/network security concerns

EXPERIENCE

I.T Solution Ltd. | Full Stack Developer

Sept. 2020 - Aug. 2022

- Worked with REST API: Developed, maintained, and optimized the website system with admin tools and different user permissions. Cooperated in the development of the RFID reader system.
- Assisted multiple government departments in inventory management: Successfully aided over 50 government
 departments in overseeing their computer-related item inventory and ensuring seamless annual audits. Created and
 administered a website application for an item borrowing system, incorporating administrative functionalities and
 diverse user permissions. The system was tailored for electronic devices like laptops, USBs, monitors, etc.
 Employed ZPL for RFID labels linked to products and developed controlled software for efficient backend data
 connectivity and management.
- Designed and Implemented backend services, regularly maintained user data, and monitored system activity on a
 daily basis.
- Ensured Server Security and Compliance: Regularly adhered to government security policies, updated server security levels, and ensured the protection of the server.
- Test Case Design and Documentation: Designed and executed test cases, and wrote related documents for debugging code.

Fun Town Hong Kong Limited | Full Stack Programmer

Jul. 2018 – Sept. 2020

- Designed and executed various projects, including creating a comprehensive website, establishing a gaming event platform, developing a mobile gaming app, and crafting administrative tools. These tools were utilized for both iOS and Android versions, enhancing user data management, and driving revenue growth through strategic initiatives.
- Maintained server activity and cooperated monthly with the Korean developer team for patch updates. Regularly monitored and updated the server to ensure its security protection.

VTM Digital Limited | Software Developer

Jul. 2017 - Jul. 2018

• Provided services for different interactive events to 30+ companies of various sizes within one year.

- Developed programming code for the website, photo booth, application, and games (AR & Mobile (iOS & Android) & VR & Kinect game).
 - * (e.g. The shopping mall photo competition event, catching game, VR pinball games, and mobile app notifications for weekly promotions for the shopping malls to attract customers.)
- Utilized AWS to establish the database structure and configure scheduled events for specific occurrences, and employed GoDaddy to purchase the domain.
- Established documents for internal records of the company.
- Analyzed project issues, such as controller movement, data transmission, data reception, security, and encryption, etc.

PROJECTS

HairSalon Website | Wix

Feb. 2021 – Present

- Developed a full-stack web application for a hair salon to display their services to customers.
- Experimented with Wix API's to get chat data from the given channel
- Through Wix to get feedback and suggested features
- Solved problems relating to booking

EDUCATION

Centennial College

Post-Graduate Certificate in Project Management

University of the West of England

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education

Higher Diploma in Game Software Development

May. 2022 – Dec. 2022

GPA: 3.411/4.0

Sept. 2016 – Aug. 2017

 $Second\ Class\ Honours (Upper\ Division)$

Sept. 2014 – Aug. 2016

GPA: 3.28/4.0

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

Its Tea, Scarborough, Toronto | Barista (Part-time)

Feb. 2023 – Present

- Managed the inventory
- Made 150+ beverages in one day

Kin-Kin Bubble tea, Scarborough, Toronto | Barista (Part-time)

Feb. 2023 - Present

- Introduced new products and promotions
- Conduct 100+ transactions in a day